The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Bunch of losers !
All the disciples in the capital were killed.
How will I explain this to the Master ?
Was the Spirit Vein of the capital affected ?
No Sect Leader, everything is normal.
Wu Cunsu
Tiandao Sect Leader
Early stage Nascent Soul
Good.
We won't make a fuss about this then.
Go tell the Master I request a meeting.
I have something to tell him.
Sect Leader,
since we are in the Tiandao Sect,
shouldn't you ask him to meet you ?
He's just a Teng Family branch member.
Shut up !
Don't bring this matter ever again.
If the Master hears about it,
I won't save your ass.
Let go of me.
Don't...
Sit down, sit down !
Teng Xuan
Branch of the Teng Family
Early stage Core Formation
Good boy.
Master.
Wu Cunsu,
is an old dog obedient because it's old
or is it old because it's obedient ?
I don't think your Ancestors understood this concept.
Master,
the Tiandao Sect is under your command.
How's it going in the capital ?
A few disciples were hurt by a criminal.
It's nothing serious.
Do not worry about it.
I don't care how many of your disciples are hurt or dead.
But if something happens to what you're protecting...
The Teng Family
won't hesitate to replace you.
Absolutely.
I'm going to the capital to catch the criminal.
Tiandao Sect Leader,
What's going on ?
come out now.
He's Early stage Nascent Soul, like me.
But he broke the formation in one move.
I'd rather not anger him.
Fellow cultivator,
how did I offend you ?
Why did you attack the formation ?
Teng
Wu Cunsu...
What are you talking about ?
Bold of you
to trespass on the Teng Family's territory.
Kill him
and refine his Nascent Soul.
The Teng Family is able to control the Tiandao Sect...
The country of Zhao really has changed...
All the Spirit Roots,
can't be to just feed this Core Formation Junior.
Something's wrong.
If you won't kill him,
someone else will.
And they will also deal with you.
Useless Sect Leader...
Wu Cunsu...
Don't forget who the country of Zhao belongs to.
Junior,
the Tiandao Sect is not a place for you to run rampant.
You will die for it !
Die !
He killed Wu Cunsu in one move...
He...
What kind of cultivation does he have ?
You,
tell me.
What's the secret plan of the Teng Family ?
Let go of me !
How dare you touch me ?
My Ancestor, Teng Huayuan, won't let you live !
He's very protective.
Just wait and see.
If you dare to hurt me, he'll tear you apart !
I...
am lucky to have met you !
Please spare my life !
I'll tell you everything !
Senior,
this is a map of all the Spirit Veins in Zhao.
These veins were built by the Ancestor.
They are used to extract Spirit Roots of mortals
to feed the Teng Family.
This thing is actually hidden
underneath the country of Zhao.
The Spirit Vein is located at the bottom of the mountain gate.
The disciples of Tiandao Sect usually take care of it.
If Senior wants to see it...
It is indeed the Spirit Roots of mortals.
They use the mortals of a country to raise the Teng Family.
Teng Huayuan
you're down to using such cruel methods
for your own benefits.
How did you extract the Spirit Roots from the mortals ?
This...
Xu Liguo.
You defy my Master like that ?
You must have a death wish.
Senior,
Senior, let me talk !
Let me talk !
I haven't eaten enough yet !
You are such an ungrateful guy.
Each sect that guards a Spirit Vein
has a formation
to absorb the Spirit Roots of mortals
and transport them through the Veins to feed the Teng Family.
How dare you hurt me ?
I will pay you back a hundredfold
until you wish you were dead.
Who's this person you're trying to call here ?
That's...
Old Man Ji Mo.
Let's meet him then.
Immortal Ji Mo is here,
everybody make way.
This flower carriage...
It's really Immortal Ji Mo !
Immortal Ji Mo,
you said you'd give me a treasure to increase my cultivation.
That was already 3 days ago.
You didn't forget did you ?
Right ?
Old man Ji Mo
Teng  Family Guest Elder
Middle stage Nascent Soul
I wouldn't dare to.
In Zhao, there is nothing that I, Immortal Ji Mo, cannot do.
Forget about the treasure,
let's kill a few Foundation Establishments brats
so you can use their blood
to replenish your vitality.
Isn't it a great idea ?
Immortal Ji Mo,
is this something urgent ?
Don't you want to be with me ?
Get lost !
Please spare my life.
I must act fast,
I must act fast !
If another Teng Family Member dies because of me,
this will be bad !
Fellow cultivator !
Spare Teng Xuan's life, we can discuss this matter.
I destroyed the Spirit Vein.
Old man Ji Mo,
do you think this can be discussed ?
I don't know where this Early stage Nascent Soul came from.
In any case,
fighting him isn't worth it.
Fellow cultivator,
you must not be aware
but there are 9 branches of Spirit Veins.
They are all built by the Teng Family.
The one under the Tiandao Sect is just an auxilary.
If the Spirit Vein is destroyed, it can be rebuilt.
But the dead cannot come back to life.
Fellow cultivator,
come with me to Teng Family City
and apologize to the Teng Patriarch.
And this matter is settled.
It looks like
Old man Ji Mo has been living
quite a good life lately.
Fellow cultivator,
have we met before ?
It seems that fellow cultivator is not from the country of Zhao.
Zhao is under the control of the Teng Family.
The 9 Spirit Veins are not used by normal people.
They nourish 9 powerful Nascent Soul Core Members !
The other sects
have to rely on the Teng Family.
Not to mention us rogue cultivators.
9 Nascent Soul cultivators ?
Yes.
For 200 years,
the Teng Patriarch has been working hard
to build the Spirit Veins.
He has nourished 9 Nascent Soul cultivators
to push the Teng Family to the number one spot.
And the Teng Patriarch himself,
is not someone you can offend.
Listen to this old man.
Never, ever kill the Teng Family.
You...
You don't know your place !
You could've just apologized.
But now, I can only take your head as compensation !
You are just a lowly Early stage Nascent Soul
yet you dare to act arrogantly in front of me !?
Slash !
Fellow cultivator,
let's talk this out !
Let's talk this out !
Do you know why I want to kill the Teng Family ?
Fellow cultivator,
I don't know what grudges you have with the Teng Family.
I'm just a Guest Elder serving the Teng.
400 years ago,
you had a disciple called Bai Zhan, I killed him.
Do you remember ?
He deserved it.
But you paid and assassin
and caused a commotion in Teng Family City.
In the end,
so many people were killed...
It's you ?
That Qi Condensation brat !
I wanted to eat his Nascent Soul...
But looking at the way Master is,
I'd rather not touch it.
Teng Huayuan...
Since you like those 9 Nascent Soul so much,
I will kill them
one by one.
I will destroy them
I want you to see your Teng Family
get wiped out !
I've had my share of wounds,
now I want to fight back.
Is my destiny a wall of restrictions
that's blocking all my hopes
for life ?
My flesh and blood witnessed the past,
my adversity pushed me to brave the waves.
How do you navigate through the years passing by ?
Nirvana and rebirth are no longer
out of reach.
Immortals
are obsessed with delusions of grandeur.
Renegades
seek to crush the impermanence of the heavens.
Don't tell me that I overestimate myself
and that the path to revenge leads to hell
because I don't see the harm in that.
My new body opens its eyes
and awakens from its dream.
I have overcome many trials
to get this body back.
No matter how many endless dark nights go by,
I can still see.
By sticking to this thought, I will get it done
by my own hands.
Returning to my body opened my eyes,
I need to continue my Immortal journey.
With a flick of a finger,
only my indomitable heart remains.
Life and death trials temper me, I am not afraid of losing my soul.
Even if there are countless tribulations and hardships.
Overcome this fate, smash through the obstacles,
like the descent of a god.